Hello everyone my name is Anuja we were going today, do
you guys care what, then we come to
Anuja's place, just like every girlfriend
robs her friend's money, she
robs my money, Pyari understood that she had paid the money
herself on the phone, went to return the charging cable for
it, then we leave for
Kalyanpur where we were supposed to go,
in Papa village we forgot the way, we did
not reach where we were supposed to go, instead we reached another place, finally we have
reached friend's village and we ploughed
friend's road, we felt so good after coming, don't even
ask, we got to see beautiful places here,
friend had finished Nagar Jati,
then we go towards home,
my friend has made a plan to
play DJ, that's why we came to see him
and there is a sound checkup here, the DJ was
good but we thought that we will come after a few days
and we leave for Ambikapur and then
we come to eat Dabli next to Vishal Begum Haat,
then we have come, we are eating ice cream, we had reached
Sauriya Bhaiya's place, then we reached
Girls College  If you like my video then please
like, comment, share and follow me
also.